Syed Abbas



zamanatabbasnaqvi@gmail.com



+92 3232629249



linkedin.com/in/syed-zamanat-abbas

Summary

I have been a Python developer for the last 2 years. My main goal is to fully understand the client's tasks and bring them to life. I use the best ways in web development and try to keep up to date with all web industry innovations.

Besides, I have a bachelor's degree in Data Science from the University of Karachi and, I graduated in the "Web development by javascript and python" course from Harward University. Creative skills make me more confident in this project.

I am adequate in prominent skills like Python, Django, Flask, Html, CSS & JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax, API development, SQLite, Mysql, Postgresql, MongoDB, and different web hosting sectors, and so on. I am passionate about websites and back-end coding. I like to play with codes and results in the best output from my work.

Experience



Django and Flask Developer

Fiverr

Mar 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month +) https://www.fiverr.com/share/YmgW1I

Backend Django and Flask Developer

Webtrica

Sep 2021 - Present (7 months +)

Account Assistant

Gul Ahmed Textile Mills Limited Apr 2018 - Sep 2018 (6 months)

Education



Karachi University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Data Science and Statistics

Licenses & Certifications



Introduction to Computer Science - CS50

https://cs50.harvard.edu/certificates/b60121a6-f484-432f-ae3b-0cc7eabd0837



Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Django REST Framework • Flask • JavaScript • MySQL • MongoDB • jQuery • API Development • Mobile Applications • Amazon Web Services (AWS)